export default data = [
  {
      question: "This dress is pretty, ______ it does not look good on me",
      options: ["so","but","or","if"],
      correct_option: "but"
  },
  {
      question: "Getting up early on a cold morning is not easy, ______?",
      options: ["are you","do you","does it","is it"],
      correct_option: "is it"
  },
  {
      question: "Tonight I’ll stay at the office until I ______ the work",
      options: ["finish","am finishing	","finished	","will finish"],
      correct_option: "finish"
  },
  {
      question: "Charles ______ a day in the department store looking for a hat for his wife",
      options: ["cost","spent","saw","made"],
      correct_option: "spent"
  },
  {
      question: "Tom ______ ten pounds over the past two months. He looks much thinner now",
      options: ["loses","has lost","will lose","was losing"],
      correct_option: "has lost"
  },
  {
      question: "I don’t like any one of these three watches. Can you show me ______ one?",
      options: ["the others","other","either","another"],
      correct_option: "another"
  },
  {
      question: "The waiters are asked to be ______; they should always smile and remember to say “Welcome” and “Please.”",
      options: ["honest","polite","special","strong"],
      correct_option: "polite"
  },
  {
      question: "On Children’s Day, Ms. Lee, a famous storybook writer, to ______ Molly’s Bookstore to talk about her new book. My two little kids just can’t wait to see her",
      options: ["came","was coming","has come","is going to come"],
      correct_option: "is going to come"
  },
  {
      question: "No one thought James would appear at Katie’s party. So when he ______, everyone was surprised and could not believe their eyes",
      options: ["would","was","had","did"],
      correct_option: "did"
  },
  {
      question: "B&J Café ______ known as the tallest building in town. However, O&G Restaurant became the tallest building in",
      options: ["has been","had been","is","would be"],
      correct_option: "had been"
  },
  {
      question: "Actor David Piper became tired of talking about the movie ______ after he was interviewed about it many times",
      options: ["he is famous","that he is famous","that is famous for","he is famous for"],
      correct_option: "he is famous for"
  },
]
